Last update: 5/24/2022



Kourosh Ahmadzadeh Ataei

Gmail | in Github | in Linkedin

Personal Data

Address: No.226, Dehkhoda 7 St., Piruzi Blvd., Mashhad, IRAN.

Mobile: +989036928421

Date of birth: December 19, 1996. (25 years)

Place of birth: Ferdows, IRAN

Education

Ferdowsi University of Mashhad (FUM)

Bachelor of Computer Engineering GPA 15.56/20 (3.31 GPA)

Mashhad, IRAN Sep. 2016 - Sep. 2021

- Last 2 years GPA is 16.59 (3.52 GPA)
- Relevant Coursework: Data Mining Algorithm Design Database Information Retrieval Artificial Intelligence Web Development Data communication Multimedia systems Data Structures

Areas of Interests

Computer Vision, Deep learning, Machine learning, Web development, Rest API, Blockchain, Software engineering, Information Retrieval, Data Mining

Experience

Backend Developer

Jul.2022 - Now

Angizeh Negar Khavaran (Lagrange)

I am responsible for:

- Develop backend base on python
- Datamining

Main achievement:

- Work in professional team
- Learn and implement structural project
- Work with SQLAlchemy
- Participation in datamining Project
- Work with docker

Last update: 5/24/2022

Jun. 2022 – Feb. 2022

Junior Software Engineer, Co-Founder

Al Trader startup (Aran Accelerator)

I am responsible for:

- Develop platform base on python
- Implement telegram bot
- Work with MySQL

Main achievement:

- Acquire team management Teamwork
- Learn and Implement Pattern Designs

- Sysadmin for server side
- Product manager
- Some experiences in product manager
- Participation in Al Project

R&D Developer

Green Render Startup (Aran Accelerator)

I am responsible for:

Configure render farm - multi-GPUs

Main achievement:

 learn server-side commands and bash script(ubuntu-centos)

Work with PostgreSQL

• learn research and development

Swift Developer Intern

Part software

I am responsible for:

- Develop IOS applications based on swift and objective-c
- Main achievement:
 - · Learn advance GIT
 - Learn swift and IOS development

Jul. 2020 - Sep. 2020

Jun. 2022 – Feb. 2022

- Learn swift and XCode
- Do tasks and small project

Selected Projects

Work

• Teamus website

Feb. 2022 - Present

Developed a web application for team and persons CVs & Resumes

- Based on Django python
- App provides team creation and write their CVs for customers

Cryptocurrency bot API

Apr. 2022 – Present

Develop an API for cryptocurrency bots

- Based on Django rest framework
- App provides strategies and auto trading for customers with purchase plans

Last update: 5/24/2022

Academic

Mstpd UI
 Winter 2020

Data communication, Prof.A.Hosseini, FUM

- Implemented a CLI for Multiple Spanning Tree Protocol Daemon project with configure and installation on Ubuntu based on python
- Optimization on TF-IDF recommender system

Fall 2020

Basics of information retrieval and web search, Prof.F.Ensan, FUM.

 Implemented an optimization on classical TF-IDF algorithm and proposed adaptive weight of position of word algorithm based on TF-IDF

Network security API

Winter 2019

Fundamentals of Secure Computing, Prof.H.Amintoosi, FUM

- o Implemented an API with Django Rest API for check ports, show user logs, Token Authentication System, check available website user requests, DDoS prevention
- <u>Charity website</u> Fall 2019

Principles of Database Design, Prof.B.behkamal, FUM

- Implemented a free food distribution web application for charities and restaurant based on PHP and MySQL.
- Air Hockey
 Winter 2016

Advanced Programming, Prof.A.Nouri Baygi, FUM

JavaFx game application with AI agent

Skills

Languages: (advance)Python, familiar with SQL, Html, CSS, Java, Swift, bash script

Languages: (basic)Java, Solidity, PHP, C

Libraries: NumPy, Pandas, Multithreading, Django, Django REST framework, scrapy, requests

Technologies & Principles: Clean coding & SOLID, OOP, Linux distributions, Git, PyCharm, Google Colab,

XCode, CEH, MVC, Design Patterns, Scrum, fast API, Telegram bot

Languages: English: Upper Intermediate, Persian: Native

About Me

I learned all of my big major of these skills independently although I am **team player** and I willing to **teamwork**. I am **flexible**, **punctual**, **diligent**, **ethical**, **loyal** and **accountable** at work and learn **quickly**. Learning new languages and frameworks enable me to research and develop more and more.